const _0x519fc2=_0x3aa3;(function(_0x4794bb,_0x5890d9){const _0x7fc69c=_0x3aa3,_0x372d64=_0x4794bb();while(!![]){try{const _0x5676b5=-parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x1a3))/0x1+-parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x159))/0x2*(parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x16e))/0x3)+parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x15b))/0x4*(parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x1b6))/0x5)+parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x19b))/0x6+parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x1da))/0x7*(-parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x194))/0x8)+-parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x1b5))/0x9*(parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x1cd))/0xa)+-parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x200))/0xb*(-parseInt(_0x7fc69c(0x162))/0xc);if(_0x5676b5===_0x5890d9)break;else _0x372d64['push'](_0x372d64['shift']());}catch(_0xa0dde3){_0x372d64['push'](_0x372d64['shift']());}}}(_0x31f0,0x1ae35));const riddles=[{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1bd),'options':['0',_0x519fc2(0x208),'100','45'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1c9),'options':['Friends',_0x519fc2(0x1db),'A\x20party',_0x519fc2(0x1cb)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1db)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x169),'options':['0','1','2',_0x519fc2(0x205)],'answer':'2'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1f6),'options':['0','1','2','4'],'answer':'2'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x20b),'options':['2','4','6',_0x519fc2(0x1b2)],'answer':'4'},{'question':'What\x20comes\x20next:\x201,\x201,\x202,\x203,\x205,\x208,\x20___?','options':['10','11','12','13'],'answer':'13'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1b0),'options':['5\x20times',_0x519fc2(0x190),_0x519fc2(0x209),_0x519fc2(0x1c5)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x190)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x160),'options':['7','21','28','35'],'answer':'21'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1cc),'options':['1','2','3','5'],'answer':'2'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1eb),'options':['1','4','7','10'],'answer':'4'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1ac),'options':['1','12',_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1f3)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1f3)},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20next\x20number\x20in\x20this\x20sequence:\x2010,\x209,\x2060,\x2090,\x2070,\x2066,\x20___?','options':['80','96',_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1f1)],'answer':'96'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1b4),'options':['$1',_0x519fc2(0x178),_0x519fc2(0x19e),_0x519fc2(0x1b9)],'answer':'$1'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x18d),'options':['13','24','39','48'],'answer':'39'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1b1),'options':['2','7',_0x519fc2(0x1dd),'All\x20of\x20them'],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1dd)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x156),'options':['0',_0x519fc2(0x1c7),'32',_0x519fc2(0x1fe)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1c7)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1b7),'options':['25','1','30','5'],'answer':'1'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20spelled\x20with\x20letters\x20in\x20alphabetical\x20order?','options':['1','40','100',_0x519fc2(0x197)],'answer':'40'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x279\x27\x20appear\x20between\x201\x20and\x20100?','options':['10','19','20','21'],'answer':'20'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1df),'options':['1','2','3','4'],'answer':'3'},{'question':'If\x20a\x20doctor\x20gives\x20you\x203\x20pills\x20and\x20tells\x20you\x20to\x20take\x20one\x20every\x20half\x20hour,\x20how\x20long\x20will\x20they\x20last?','options':[_0x519fc2(0x154),_0x519fc2(0x1ec),_0x519fc2(0x1ca),'3\x20hours'],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x154)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1c2),'options':['9','12','18','27'],'answer':'18'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x192),'options':['12','13','14','15'],'answer':'13'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1b8),'options':['99','100',_0x519fc2(0x180),_0x519fc2(0x1a2)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x180)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x19c),'options':['25','50','70',_0x519fc2(0x1fe)],'answer':'70'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e7),'options':['1','16','64',_0x519fc2(0x1fe)],'answer':'64'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1bb),'options':['3','4','5','6'],'answer':'5'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20multiplied\x20by\x20their\x20product?','options':['0','1',_0x519fc2(0x18e),_0x519fc2(0x19f)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x18e)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1a0),'options':['20',_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1f1),_0x519fc2(0x1ba)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1f1)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x171),'options':['0','1','-1','Infinity'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e8),'options':['7','8','10','It\x20depends\x20on\x20the\x20paper'],'answer':'7'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1c2),'options':['9','12','18','27'],'answer':'18'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e5),'options':['2\x20apples',_0x519fc2(0x1ee),'6\x20apples',_0x519fc2(0x174)],'answer':'A\x20lot\x20of\x20friends'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x19a),'options':['30','60','90',_0x519fc2(0x1f1)],'answer':'60'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20sides\x20does\x20a\x20snowflake\x20have?','options':['4','6','8','10'],'answer':'6'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1f4),'options':['1','4','7','10'],'answer':'1'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x20e),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x154),_0x519fc2(0x1ca),_0x519fc2(0x181),_0x519fc2(0x1fb)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1ca)},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20their\x20product?','options':['0','1','19','39'],'answer':'19'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1f0),'options':['5','10','15','20'],'answer':'10'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1f8),'options':['0','1','2','3'],'answer':'1'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x16f),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1dc),'12\x20per\x20year','None',_0x519fc2(0x1a7)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1dd)},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20one\x20more\x20than\x20the\x20product\x20of\x20its\x20digits?','options':['1','9','19','25'],'answer':'19'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1c1),'options':['16','20','30','40'],'answer':'30'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20multiplied\x20by\x20two?','options':['0','12','18','36'],'answer':'18'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x16a),'options':['2','4','8',_0x519fc2(0x204)],'answer':'8'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x191),'options':['0','6','8','9'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x195),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1ba),_0x519fc2(0x1e0),'400'],'answer':'300'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x158),'options':['0','1',_0x519fc2(0x18e),_0x519fc2(0x19f)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x18e)},{'question':'If\x20you\x20count\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100,\x20how\x20many\x209\x27s\x20will\x20you\x20pass?','options':['10','19','20','21'],'answer':'20'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20their\x20cubes?','options':['0','1',_0x519fc2(0x1d4),'370'],'answer':'153'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20can\x20you\x20subtract\x2010\x20from\x20100?','options':['10\x20times',_0x519fc2(0x190),'90\x20times','Never'],'answer':'Once'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x17d),'options':['0','12','18','36'],'answer':'18'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x185),'options':['10','20','21','30'],'answer':'21'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x186),'options':['0','12','27','36'],'answer':'27'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x18a),'options':['10','11','12','20'],'answer':'11'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x17e),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'12'},{'question':'If\x20you\x20have\x2010\x20fish\x20and\x205\x20drown,\x20how\x20many\x20are\x20left?','options':['5','10','15',_0x519fc2(0x1d3)],'answer':'10'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x182),'options':['0','12','24','36'],'answer':'12'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1d9),'options':['10','15','20','25'],'answer':'20'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20three\x20times\x20their\x20product?','options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x166),'options':['1','2','3','5'],'answer':'2'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e9),'options':['0','12','25','50'],'answer':'0'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x272\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','options':['10','15','20','25'],'answer':'20'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1d0),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':'If\x20you\x20have\x205\x20apples\x20and\x20you\x20eat\x203,\x20what\x20do\x20you\x20have?','options':[_0x519fc2(0x1bf),_0x519fc2(0x165),_0x519fc2(0x170),_0x519fc2(0x18b)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x18b)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1ed),'options':['0','12','18','36'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x184),'options':['10','15','20','25'],'answer':'20'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20five\x20times\x20their\x20product?','options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':'If\x20you\x20have\x2010\x20cookies\x20and\x20you\x20give\x20away\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have?','options':['5','10','15','20'],'answer':'5'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20seven?','options':['0','12','21','42'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x15f),'options':['10','15','20','25'],'answer':'20'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x203),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1a4),'options':['3','6','9','12'],'answer':'6'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1c3),'options':['0','12','24','48'],'answer':'0'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x276\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','options':['10','15','20','25'],'answer':'20'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1fd),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1be),'options':['4','8','16',_0x519fc2(0x15a)],'answer':'4'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20nine?','options':['0','12','18','36'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x206),'options':['10','15','20','25'],'answer':'20'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1aa),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x207),'options':['6','12','18','A\x20mess'],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1f2)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x20c),'options':['0','12','20','40'],'answer':'0'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x279\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','options':['10','15','20','25'],'answer':'20'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1d5),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':'If\x20you\x20have\x2020\x20marbles\x20and\x20you\x20lose\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have\x20left?','options':['10','20','30','40'],'answer':'10'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x183),'options':['0','12','22','44'],'answer':'0'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x270\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1a5),_0x519fc2(0x1ba),'300'],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1a5)},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20ten\x20times\x20their\x20product?','options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e3),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1ab),_0x519fc2(0x1a9),_0x519fc2(0x19d),_0x519fc2(0x20d)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x20d)},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20twelve?','options':['0','12','24','36'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x173),'options':['100',_0x519fc2(0x1ba),'300',_0x519fc2(0x16d)],'answer':'300'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1c0),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1ad),'options':['0','1','2',_0x519fc2(0x16c)],'answer':'2'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x17b),'options':['0','12','26','52'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1de),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),'200','300','400'],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1e0)},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20twelve\x20times\x20their\x20product?','options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x177),'options':['5','10','15','20'],'answer':'10'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e4),'options':['0','12','28','56'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x202),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1ba),_0x519fc2(0x1e0),'400'],'answer':'300'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x17a),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x15d),'options':['5','10','15','20'],'answer':'10'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1ff),'options':['0','12','30','60'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x17f),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1ba),_0x519fc2(0x1e0),'400'],'answer':'300'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x193),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x167),'options':['1','2','3',_0x519fc2(0x1dd)],'answer':'1'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x20f),'options':['0','12','32','64'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x164),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1ba),'300',_0x519fc2(0x16d)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1e0)},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20fifteen\x20times\x20their\x20product?','options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':'If\x20you\x20have\x206\x20donuts\x20and\x20you\x20eat\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have\x20left?','options':['3','6','9','12'],'answer':'3'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x172),'options':['0','12','34','68'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e6),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1ba),'300',_0x519fc2(0x16d)],'answer':'300'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x187),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x168),'options':['$0.25','$1','$4',_0x519fc2(0x1fa)],'answer':'$1'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e1),'options':['0','12','36','72'],'answer':'0'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x277\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),_0x519fc2(0x1ba),_0x519fc2(0x1e0),_0x519fc2(0x16d)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1e0)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1e2),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':'If\x20you\x20have\x202\x20noses\x20and\x20you\x20lose\x201,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have\x20left?','options':['0','1','2',_0x519fc2(0x1c8)],'answer':'1'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x15c),'options':['0','12','38','76'],'answer':'0'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x199),'options':[_0x519fc2(0x1fe),'200',_0x519fc2(0x1e0),_0x519fc2(0x16d)],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1e0)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x175),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':'If\x20you\x20have\x2010\x20fingers\x20and\x20you\x20wear\x20gloves\x20on\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20fingers\x20are\x20covered?','options':['5','10','15','20'],'answer':'10'},{'question':'What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20twenty?','options':['0','12','40','80'],'answer':'0'},{'question':'How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x279\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','options':['100','200',_0x519fc2(0x1e0),'400'],'answer':_0x519fc2(0x1e0)},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x1ef),'options':['0','1','12','24'],'answer':'24'},{'question':_0x519fc2(0x201),'options':['0','1','99','100'],'answer':'1'}];let selectedRiddles=[],currentQuestion=0x0,score=0x0;function _0x3aa3(_0x4eaa98,_0x347393){const _0x31f016=_0x31f0();return _0x3aa3=function(_0x3aa336,_0x28d06a){_0x3aa336=_0x3aa336-0x154;let _0x5995d9=_0x31f016[_0x3aa336];return _0x5995d9;},_0x3aa3(_0x4eaa98,_0x347393);}function startGame(){const _0x55bb83=_0x519fc2;selectedRiddles=[...riddles][_0x55bb83(0x1ea)](()=>0.5-Math[_0x55bb83(0x1a8)]())[_0x55bb83(0x1bc)](0x0,0xa),currentQuestion=0x0,score=0x0,document['getElementById'](_0x55bb83(0x179))[_0x55bb83(0x157)][_0x55bb83(0x188)]=_0x55bb83(0x1f7),document[_0x55bb83(0x1d2)](_0x55bb83(0x1d7))[_0x55bb83(0x157)][_0x55bb83(0x188)]=_0x55bb83(0x1f7),document['getElementById']('intro')[_0x55bb83(0x157)]['display']=_0x55bb83(0x1f7),document[_0x55bb83(0x1d2)](_0x55bb83(0x1ce))[_0x55bb83(0x157)][_0x55bb83(0x188)]=_0x55bb83(0x1f9),showQuestion();}function showQuestion(){const _0x12a29c=_0x519fc2,_0x1fe84d=selectedRiddles[currentQuestion];document[_0x12a29c(0x1d2)](_0x12a29c(0x198))['innerText']='Q'+(currentQuestion+0x1)+':\x20'+_0x1fe84d[_0x12a29c(0x198)],document[_0x12a29c(0x1d2)](_0x12a29c(0x1d6))[_0x12a29c(0x18c)]='Question\x20'+(currentQuestion+0x1)+_0x12a29c(0x196);const _0x428a1d=document[_0x12a29c(0x1d2)](_0x12a29c(0x15e));_0x428a1d[_0x12a29c(0x1d8)]='',_0x1fe84d['options']['forEach']((_0x79ac47,_0x4532bf)=>{const _0x1d75a1=_0x12a29c,_0x56852e=document[_0x1d75a1(0x1c4)](_0x1d75a1(0x1b3));_0x56852e[_0x1d75a1(0x176)][_0x1d75a1(0x1af)](_0x1d75a1(0x163));const _0x36c683=document[_0x1d75a1(0x1c4)](_0x1d75a1(0x20a));_0x36c683['type']=_0x1d75a1(0x1c6),_0x36c683['name']=_0x1d75a1(0x161),_0x36c683[_0x1d75a1(0x17c)]=_0x79ac47,_0x36c683['required']=!![],_0x56852e[_0x1d75a1(0x18f)](_0x36c683),_0x56852e[_0x1d75a1(0x18f)](document[_0x1d75a1(0x155)](_0x79ac47)),_0x428a1d[_0x1d75a1(0x18f)](_0x56852e);});}function _0x31f0(){const _0x121696=['How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x278\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','What\x20is\x20the\x20smallest\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20divisible\x20by\x201\x20through\x206?','450240xFpxzK','If\x20you\x20divide\x2030\x20by\x20half\x20and\x20add\x2010,\x20what\x20do\x20you\x20get?','100\x20pennies','$10','144','If\x20you\x20write\x20all\x20the\x20numbers\x20from\x20300\x20to\x20400,\x20how\x20many\x20times\x20will\x20you\x20write\x20the\x20digit\x20\x273\x27?','Play\x20Again','99!','26017MzLSxN','If\x20you\x20have\x206\x20pairs\x20of\x20shoes\x20and\x20lose\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have\x20left?','192','🎉\x20You\x20scored\x20','Depends\x20on\x20the\x20rooster','random','99\x20pennies','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20eight\x20times\x20their\x20product?','1\x20penny','How\x20many\x20eggs\x20can\x20you\x20put\x20in\x20an\x20empty\x20basket\x20that\x20is\x2012\x20inches\x20across?','If\x20you\x20have\x20an\x20empty\x20box\x20and\x20you\x20add\x20two\x20apples,\x20how\x20many\x20apples\x20are\x20in\x20the\x20box?','block','add','How\x20many\x20times\x20can\x20you\x20subtract\x205\x20from\x2025?','How\x20many\x20animals\x20did\x20Moses\x20take\x20on\x20the\x20ark?','The\x20whole\x20pizza','label','If\x20a\x20dozen\x20eggs\x20cost\x2012\x20cents,\x20how\x20much\x20does\x20100\x20eggs\x20cost?','9EqoCXN','150425ycUTKh','If\x201=5,\x202=10,\x203=15,\x204=20,\x20what\x20does\x205\x20equal?','What\x20is\x20the\x20largest\x20number\x20you\x20can\x20write\x20using\x20only\x20two\x20digits?','1\x20cent\x20per\x20egg','200','How\x20many\x20zeros\x20are\x20in\x20one\x20hundred\x20thousand?','slice','What\x20number\x20do\x20you\x20get\x20when\x20you\x20multiply\x20all\x20the\x20numbers\x20on\x20a\x20telephone\x27s\x20number\x20pad?','If\x20you\x20have\x208\x20candies\x20and\x20you\x20eat\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have?','2\x20apples','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20eleven\x20times\x20their\x20product?','How\x20many\x20squares\x20are\x20in\x20a\x204x4\x20grid?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20twice\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20eight?','createElement','Never','radio','-40','Still\x201','If\x20two\x27s\x20company\x20and\x20three\x27s\x20a\x20crowd,\x20what\x20are\x20four\x20and\x20five?','2\x20hours','Seven','If\x20you\x20have\x203\x20apples\x20and\x20you\x20take\x20away\x202,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have?','750090qrZRHB','next-btn','hello','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20four\x20times\x20their\x20product?','Haha...\x20you\x20cannot\x20find\x20answers\x20in\x20the\x20code\x20for\x20the\x20quiz\x20...Do\x20not\x20think\x20smart\x20stupid...','getElementById','Fish\x20can\x27t\x20drown','153','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20nine\x20times\x20their\x20product?','questionnumber','start-btn','innerHTML','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x275\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','7LCpQuW','Nine','1\x20per\x20day','None','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x272\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','What\x20is\x20half\x20of\x202\x20plus\x202?','300','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20eighteen?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20seventeen\x20times\x20their\x20product?','If\x20you\x20have\x20100\x20pennies\x20and\x20you\x20give\x20away\x2099,\x20what\x20do\x20you\x20have?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20fourteen?','If\x20you\x20have\x206\x20apples\x20and\x20you\x20give\x20away\x204,\x20what\x20do\x20you\x20have?','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x276\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','What\x20is\x20the\x20smallest\x20positive\x20integer\x20that\x20is\x20a\x20perfect\x20square\x20and\x20perfect\x20cube?','How\x20many\x20times\x20can\x20you\x20fold\x20a\x20piece\x20of\x20paper\x20in\x20half?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20five?','sort','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20has\x20the\x20same\x20number\x20of\x20letters\x20as\x20its\x20meaning?','1.5\x20hours','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20six?','4\x20apples','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20nineteen\x20times\x20their\x20product?','How\x20many\x20triangles\x20are\x20in\x20a\x20pentagram?','120','A\x20mess','Only\x20one,\x20then\x20it\x27s\x20not\x20empty','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20spelled\x20with\x20letters\x20in\x20reverse\x20alphabetical\x20order?','\x20out\x20of\x207!','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20even\x20prime\x20number?','none','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20the\x20numbers\x20before\x20it?','inline-block','A\x20dollar\x20and\x20a\x20song','Depends\x20on\x20the\x20stops','log','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20seven\x20times\x20their\x20product?','100','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20fifteen?','230428VsjAKe','If\x20you\x20have\x20100\x20problems\x20and\x20math\x20solves\x2099,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have\x20left?','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x273\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20six\x20times\x20their\x20product?','Still\x20hungry','Infinite','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x278\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','If\x20you\x20have\x2012\x20eggs\x20and\x20you\x20drop\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have?','362880','25\x20times','input','If\x20a\x20pizza\x20is\x20divided\x20into\x208\x20slices\x20and\x20you\x20eat\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20slices\x20are\x20left?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20ten?','A\x20generous\x20heart','If\x20a\x20train\x20leaves\x20the\x20station\x20at\x2060\x20mph,\x20how\x20long\x20will\x20it\x20take\x20to\x20travel\x20120\x20miles?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20sixteen?','1\x20hour','createTextNode','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20temperature\x20that\x20is\x20the\x20same\x20in\x20Celsius\x20and\x20Fahrenheit?','style','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20their\x20product?','26wAqBAO','A\x20sugar\x20rush','8TZohTi','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20nineteen?','If\x20you\x20have\x2010\x20toes\x20and\x20you\x20wear\x20socks\x20on\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20toes\x20are\x20covered?','options-form','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x274\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','What\x20is\x20the\x20smallest\x20whole\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20seven\x20times\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits?','answer','168owkLeb','option','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x275\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','3\x20apples','If\x20you\x20have\x203\x20oranges\x20and\x20you\x20take\x20away\x202,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have?','If\x20you\x20have\x203\x20wishes\x20and\x20you\x20use\x202,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have\x20left?','If\x20you\x20have\x204\x20quarters,\x20how\x20much\x20money\x20do\x20you\x20have?','How\x20many\x20sides\x20does\x20a\x20circle\x20have?','If\x20you\x20have\x204\x20apples\x20and\x20you\x20divide\x20them\x20by\x20half,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have?','input[name=\x22answer\x22]:checked','Still\x20empty','400','9159LPBlcy','If\x20you\x20buy\x20a\x20rooster\x20to\x20lay\x20eggs,\x20how\x20many\x20eggs\x20will\x20you\x20get?','5\x20apples','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20integer\x20that\x20is\x20neither\x20positive\x20nor\x20negative?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20seventeen?','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x271\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','A\x20lot\x20of\x20friends','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20eighteen\x20times\x20their\x20product?','classList','If\x20you\x20have\x205\x20fingers\x20on\x20one\x20hand\x20and\x205\x20on\x20the\x20other,\x20how\x20many\x20do\x20you\x20have\x20total?','$1.20','score','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20thirteen\x20times\x20their\x20product?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20thirteen?','value','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20two?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20twice\x20their\x20product?','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x274\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','9^9','3\x20hours','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20four?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20times\x20eleven?','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x273\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','If\x20you\x20write\x20all\x20the\x20numbers\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100,\x20how\x20many\x20times\x20will\x20you\x20write\x20the\x20digit\x20\x271\x27?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20multiplied\x20by\x20three?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20sixteen\x20times\x20their\x20product?','display','querySelector','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x270\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x20100?','A\x20full\x20stomach','innerText','What\x20is\x20the\x20smallest\x20number\x20that\x20increases\x20by\x2012\x20when\x20its\x20digits\x20are\x20reversed?','135','appendChild','Once','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20the\x20same\x20upside\x20down?','How\x20many\x20cupcakes\x20are\x20in\x20a\x20baker\x27s\x20dozen?','What\x20is\x20the\x20only\x20number\x20that\x20is\x20equal\x20to\x20the\x20sum\x20of\x20its\x20digits\x20plus\x20fourteen\x20times\x20their\x20product?','1421072rSoQoW','How\x20many\x20times\x20does\x20the\x20digit\x20\x277\x27\x20appear\x20from\x201\x20to\x201000?','\x20of\x207','1000','question'];_0x31f0=function(){return _0x121696;};return _0x31f0();}function nextQuestion(){const _0xbe1d83=_0x519fc2,_0x74e364=document[_0xbe1d83(0x189)](_0xbe1d83(0x16b));if(!_0x74e364){alert('Please\x20select\x20an\x20answer\x20before\x20proceeding.');return;}const _0x2f5b29=selectedRiddles[currentQuestion];_0x74e364[_0xbe1d83(0x17c)]===_0x2f5b29['answer']&&score++,currentQuestion++,currentQuestion<0x7?(showQuestion(),currentQuestion+0x1==0x7&&(document[_0xbe1d83(0x1d2)](_0xbe1d83(0x1ce))['innerHTML']='Submit',console[_0xbe1d83(0x1fc)](_0xbe1d83(0x1cf)))):endGame();}function endGame(){const _0x3ec5b2=_0x519fc2;document['getElementById']('question-container')['innerHTML']='',document[_0x3ec5b2(0x1d2)](_0x3ec5b2(0x179))[_0x3ec5b2(0x157)]['display']=_0x3ec5b2(0x1ae),document['getElementById'](_0x3ec5b2(0x179))[_0x3ec5b2(0x18c)]=_0x3ec5b2(0x1a6)+score+_0x3ec5b2(0x1f5),document[_0x3ec5b2(0x1d2)](_0x3ec5b2(0x1d7))['style'][_0x3ec5b2(0x188)]='block',document[_0x3ec5b2(0x1d2)](_0x3ec5b2(0x1d7))[_0x3ec5b2(0x18c)]=_0x3ec5b2(0x1a1),document[_0x3ec5b2(0x1d2)](_0x3ec5b2(0x1ce))['style'][_0x3ec5b2(0x188)]=_0x3ec5b2(0x1f7);}console[_0x519fc2(0x1fc)](_0x519fc2(0x1d1));